Hey, Yu-Gi-Oh, isn't that the 430 bell?
Uh...
Yeah, it is.
They're both late.
That's not good.
Rownie and Tiese have
never been late before.
I got a bad feeling about this.
I'm gonna go over to their dorm
and see if they're still there.
They might be on their way over, so
hold down the port till I get back.
Wait, why are you going out that way?
Use a door...
I wish he'd stop using the window.
Thank goodness, we were...
Would you happen to be a
lead disciple, Yu-Gi-Oh?
Yes, and you are?
My name is Frenika Seski,
one of the primary trainees.
I do apologize for coming to see
you without an appointment, sir.
I need your help.
I don't know who else
to ask. It's alright.
Tell me what's wrong.
I know you've gone above and beyond in
regards to my issue with Lord Zizek.
I really can't even begin
to thank you for that.
Unfortunately, tonight I received
word from him that I am too...
That is, he ordered me to perform a service
that I'm much too embarrassed to repeat.
I told Ronier and Tiese that if he
kept giving me orders like this,
there's no way I'd be able to stay here.
I'd have to leave the academy.
me.
When I told them all this,
they said they'd go try to reason
with him, but they still haven't
come back.
I'm afraid of what that could mean.
So am I.
Stay here till I get back.
So this is how they want to get even.
By hurting Ronie and Tiese.
Story.
Six.
One.
The end of the night?.
It's a lot of time!.
The dark side of the darkness?.
The beginning of the night.
The only way we can pass!.
The hope we can pass?.
The wish we will get?.
To be with the flash.
The flashback of the wind.
My eyes are filled with fire.
My voice is called to call me.
I'm in the beginning of my day.
I'll see you in the beginning of my day.
Shine it on my diamond.
I'm with my heart and my heart.
I'm with the stars.
I'm so happy when I
first started to shine.
It's time to shine!.
The lightest light will shine!.
I'll come back to the moon.
I will come back to the moon.
The shine of it.
The light is shining.
Are you?
Please, enter.
We just uncorked this 50-year-old bottle
from the Western Empire. Do join us.
Commoners never taste such delights.
I'm afraid I must decline.
Another matter brings me here.
I'd like to know if my page,
Primary Trainee Tiese Shreenan,
and Disciple Kirito's page,
Primary Trainee Ronie Arabelle?
came here this evening.
I see.
What a coincidence that those two girls
belong to Sir Kirito and yourself.
Their audaciousness was rather surprising.
Approaching such highly regarded
students as Umber and myself,
and without so much as
a formal invitation,
their lack of couth is familiar.
That said, they do need to be careful.
Assertiveness can sometimes
be construed as disrespect.
Do not agree, Disciple Eugeo.
We can talk about your
opinions another time.
I want to know where Tiese and Ronie are!
What is this?
What is the meaning of this, Lord Rios?
These measures were
unavoidable, Sir Eugeo.
Primary trainees Streenin and Arabelle
disrespected us to such a degree.
My hand was forced.
Disrespected?
They clearly forgot who
they were addressing.
These two lesser nobles
had the gall to accuse me,
a superior-ranking noble of using my page
as a means to satisfy my lustful urges.
After everything I've done to try to
guide Fernika down the proper path,
talk about ungrateful.
But lo and behold, the plot doth thicken.
They made the preposterous
claim that as Umber's roommate,
I was just as responsible
for his actions as he was.
The idea of someone like her asking me,
the eldest of a third-ranked household,
Have you no honor as a noble?
Have you ever heard such lunacy?
Sir, even if everything
happened as you described?
Tying them up and locking
them in your bedroom,
that goes way beyond your
authority to punish trainees!
You're referring to the school guidelines?
My dear Eugeo, you need to
think much larger than that.
Do you remember this passage
from the Academy's rules?
Higher Law takes precedence in all cases.
Higher Law refers to the Taboo
Index as well as basic Imperial Law.
In other words,
what I can exercise on these
girls of lower rank isn't
a result of authority given
to me by this academy,
but my power as a noble!
Such is my sovereign right!
Stop your squirming and take
your punishment like a good girl.
Leave him alone!
Hold your ground, commoner.
This judgment is being
carried out in complete
accordance with basic imperial
law and the taboo index.
To obstruct such a decree
would be deemed a criminal act.
If you take even one step closer, you will
become a criminal in the eyes of the law.
You can't do this!
My legs!
No! Please, no!
No! No!
No!
There are things you just shouldn't do,
even if there's no law against them.
At the same time, there
might be stuff you should do,
even if the laws say you shouldn't.
No! Stop! Please!
Yu-Gi-Oh! Help me! Please!
I'm begging you!
Don't let him do this!
Ronie and Tiese had the courage
to stand up for their friend!
What kind of law justifies
punishment for that?
Ryo's and Umber are going to defile them.
What kind of law does
nothing to stop them?
If upholding laws like
these is my duty, then...
Then I...
I...
What's going on?
Wait, this happened before.
This is evil.
I have to...
Stop them!
Help us! Please! Yadier!
My arm.
My arm is bleeding. Help!
It's not stopping.
My life is decreasing.
Please, Lord Raios, use
the sacred arts. No, wait.
A normal spell won't heal this in time.
Life energy, hurry, share
some of yours with me.
What a thrill.
Never before have I witnessed
someone commit such a heinous crime.
The scope of a noble's
authority only applies to
lesser nobles and
run-of-the-mill plebeian scum.
But for rogues who've broken the
taboo index, exceptions can be made.
I've never used my sword to
cut off someone's head before.
I will gain even more power from it.
You are no disciple now.
No, you are a criminal.
In accordance with the powers granted
to me as a third-ranked noble,
I, Rios Antinous, shall execute you!
Kirito...
Back off, Raios.
No way am I gonna let you hurt him.
Good of you to join the
party, Disciple Kirito.
However, I'm afraid
you're a hair too late.
This filthy swine violated the
Taboo Index and is a criminal.
So you best stand down.
I shall cut his head from his neck, just
like the heads of your precious flowers.
I don't give a damn about
your taboos or noble crap.
Eugio's a friend of mine, but
you, you're less than nothing.
You're even lower than
the goddamn goblins.
To think that not one, but two peasants
would commit such heinous crimes.
This means I can do away with
both of you at the same time.
What a joyous day this is.
Surely this is a divine blessing
from the goddess Stacia!
I got this.
That piece of junk will shatter
against my secret technique!
We'll see about that!
Well now, how is that?
You can't possibly have thought I,
Ryoz Antinus, would struggle
against a pissant like you!
Kirito...
My arms!
What have you done?
The blood, it won't stop!
Bumper!
Hurry!
Make the bleeding stop!
Untie your ropes and bind my arms! Now!
I can't do that!
If I untie this, my
life will be decreased!
You can't ask me to
violate the Taboo Index!
Hang the law!
Help me!
It's not stopping!
Umber!
Taboo! You must!
My life!
My life is...
Taboo!
My life! The blood! Taboo!
My life!
My blood!
The taboo!
My life!
Life!
The taboo!
I'll tie him off for you.
My life!
Taboo! Blood!
Taboo!
What the hell?
What happened to his Fluctlight?
What have you done to him?
He's...
Murderer!
Monster!
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me, Eugeo.
This is...
This is all my fault.
No, it's not.
You're not to blame for this. I am.
This happened because I
didn't think it through.
It isn't your fault,
Tiese. But... Yu-Gi-Oh.
You're right.
All that matters now is that
you and Trainee are safe.
I wish I got here sooner.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault this all happened.
I've seen this before,
somewhere a long time ago.
Hold on to her.
Don't let her see it!
A singular unit has been detected.
Tracing its ID.
Coordinates fixed.
Report complete.
Murder!
Monster!
He's right.
What am I?
I'm no better than those couplins.
No, Eugeo. You're human.
Same as me.
Sure, sometimes we screw up, but we
can learn from it and make it right.
That's being human.
Kirito.
Come out.
Step closer.
System Call.
Generate Luminous Element.
Reconstruct Lost Organ.
Go on. Open it. Yes, ma 'am.
Thank you for fixing it, Mrs. Zerka.
You are most welcome.
Now listen carefully.
Your escort is coming for you.
I must hand you over to them and
have no choice in the matter.
I'd like to say a few
words before that happens.
Disciple Eugeo,
breaking that seal is something
I was never able to do.
And as a result, you should
be able to go where I cannot.
Have faith in your sword
and in your friend.
Disciple Kirito, In all
the time you were here,
I never got to know who you really are.
That said, I do know everything here
will change once you reach the tower.
Even if I can't help you directly, I'll be
praying that you find the truth. Always.
I've seen this kind of blue and
gold somewhere before, but where?
I am the Integrity Knight who
oversees the capital of Senator.
I am Alice.
Sympathis 30.
Let's go.
Realize to you?